

Profile

High-energy employee ready to empower team members to surpass company objectives with effective leadership. Skilled in training employees, building job satisfaction, and solvina operational problems by tapping into personal experience and collaboration strengths. Successful at keeping customer, business and staff needs balanced and operations in line with targets. Seasoned leader ready for any team or business need with strong technical knowledge and natural leadership talents. Top-notch relationship-builder, articulate communicator and with 6 years of customer service experience. Dedicated to enabling team members to exceed business targets. Highly adaptable team member.

CONTACT

PHONE: 281-704-1557

EMAIL:

Robert07garcia14@gmail.com

ROBERT GARCIA

EDUCATION

Sam Houston State University - expected Fall 2022 B.B.A – Management, Information Systems Minor in Accounting

WORK EXPERIENCE

Buffalo Wild Wings

from 2018 - Current

Server/Cashier/Hospitality/Certified/Heart of House

- Deliver high quality training and leadership to teams to boost performance and help team members achieve performance targets.
- Help store management meet superior standards in service and quality in daily operations.

Keller Williams

from 2017-2018

Office Assistant

- Enhanced collaboration between team members by preparing meeting materials and taking clear notes to distribute to stakeholders.
- Interacted with customers professionally by phone, email, or in-person to provide information and directed to desired staff members.
- Processed payments and documented account changes for financial accuracy and transparency.
- Kept physical files and digitized records organized for easy updating and retrieval by authorized team members.

Tea2go from 2015-2016

Barista/Cashier

- Communicated with customers daily, promoting the benefits of the product
- Took orders and prepared them for the customer.
- Marked inventory of product.
- Dealt with customer questions, comments, and concerns in an effective and timely manner.

CERTIFICATIONS AND RELEVANT COURSEWORK

- CompTia Cert
- OSHA Cert
- C#/C++
- Business Systems Implementation
- Principles of MIS

REFERENCES

Shelby Klenner: (Current Employer)

Phone: 936-242-5960

Lisa Whatley Brinks: (Former Employer at Keller Williams)

Phone: 832-641-6337

Brent Boeghning: (Former Employer at Tea2Go)

Phone: 806-677-9376